<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Dignity and Debt</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Dignity and Debt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 18:11:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt in America: An Interactive Map from The Urban Institute</title>
      <link>/news/new-item-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/new-item-07/</guid>
      <description>The Urban Institute presents a new series of interactive maps of failing auto, medical, and student loans across the US. These maps visualize the geography of debt disparities that reinforce existing wealth gaps between white communities and communities of color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty Book: Frederick Wherry *04 on Extending Credit</title>
      <link>/news/new-item-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/new-item-05/</guid>
      <description>For many borrowers, obtaining a home mortgage, car loan, or credit card is a relatively simple process. A bank looks up their credit score — measured on a scale of 300 to 850 — to determine their past financial behavior. For some 45 million Americans, however, that assessment is not possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sociologist Wherry: Studying money and human values</title>
      <link>/news/new-item-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/new-item-06/</guid>
      <description>Frederick Wherry, a professor of sociology at Princeton, calls himself an “accidental sociologist.” Growing up in South Carolina with his twin sister and four brothers, he wanted to be a civil rights lawyer. During his undergraduate years, he traveled to Africa, and after graduation, Asia, leading him to aim for a career in international development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>